<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tns:plays xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xmlns:tns="http://www.example.org/playlist"
	xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="playlist.xsd">
	<play title="The Book of Mormon">
		<description>The Book of Mormon is the biggest Broadway musical smash
			in recent memory, and now it's repeating its phenomenal success in
			London.

			Its first year sold out faster than you can say 'Oh my God,
			they killed
			Kenny', and it's still red-hot. As such, we encourage you
			to book
			promptly if you fancy seeing it soon.

			The show is the
			brainchild of South Park creators Trey Parker and Matt
			Stone, with
			Robert Lopez of Avenue Q. It won an incredible 9 Tony
			Awards after
			opening at New York’s Eugene O’Neill Theatre in March
			2011, and its
			soundtrack is the biggest selling cast album for forty
			years, reaching
			No. 3 on the U.S. Billboard chart and picking up the
			Grammy Award for
			Best Musical Theatre Album.

			Sharply satirical, wildly irreverent, more
			than a bit rude but somehow sweet
			and endearing as well, The Book of
			Mormon gleefully skewers a
			truckload of sacred cows including
			organized religion, consumerism
			and the musical genre itself.
		</description>
		<dates>
			<date>2016-01-20</date>
			<date>2016-01-21</date>
			<date>2016-01-22</date>
		</dates>

	</play>
	<play title="Matilda the Musical">
		<description>Matilda the Musical is one of the West End's most
			successful and popular productions, having won seven Olivier Awards
			including Best New Musical, giving it the record for the most Olivier
			Awards won by a musical. The show has also been a hit on Broadway,
			taking home five Tony Awards, and is one of the most successful
			British musicals in recent history.

			Produced by the Royal Shakespeare
			Company, this heart-warming musical is
			based on the classic children's
			book by Roald Dahl, and follows the
			precocious heroine as she
			struggles with her family and her evil
			Headmistress, Miss Trunchbull.
			To overcome these obstacles, she
			decides to be a “little bit naughty”
			and soon discovers that she
			possesses an extraordinary gift.

			Featuring
			a sharp and witty book by Dennis Kelly and a thoroughly original
			score by comedian Tim Minchin, this incredible production has
			delighted audiences from all over the world. The extraordinarily
			talented cast of adults and children tell this 'underdog' tale in a
			highly visual and imaginative way that will have you gripped to your
			seats in amazement.
		</description>
		<dates>
			<date>2016-03-26</date>
			<date>2016-03-27</date>
		</dates>
	</play>
	<play title="Billy Elliot">
		<description>The tale of a little boy who overcomes poverty and
			prejudice to become a ballet dancer is so simple yet so uplifting
			it’s no wonder Billy Elliot became a movie classic. Billy Elliot the
			Musical, with its stunning dance sequences and inspired music by
			Elton John, is even better.

			If you haven't seen the film in a while or
			- heaven forbid - you missed
			it altogether, tickets for the multi-Tony
			Award-winning Billy Elliot
			the Musical do just as good a job of
			transporting you back to the
			sight and sounds of '80s. You may even
			feel a pang for your own
			'inner Billy Elliot' of years gone by, when
			you weren't afraid to
			dream and it felt like the world was at your
			feet.
		</description>
		<dates>
			<date>2016-03-23</date>
			<date>2016-03-25</date>
		</dates>
	</play>
	<play title="Courios incident dog">
		<description>Following its original sellout run at the NT’s Cottesloe
			theatre, Marianne Elliott’s highly acclaimed production of The
			Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time was justly rewarded
			with a West End transfer.

			Unforseen circumstances led to its run at
			the Apollo Theatre being abruptly
			curtailed in late 2013, but its now
			back in the West End at the
			Gielgud Theatre, as ingenious and
			compelling as ever.

			The play is based on Mark Haddon’s award-winning
			2003 novel about 15
			year-old Christopher Boone, who uses facts,
			forensics and systemised
			data (a symptom of his autistic-like
			behaviour) to launch an
			investigation into finding the killer of his
			neighbour’s dog.
		</description>
		<dates>
			<date>2016-03-20</date>
			<date>2016-03-24</date>
		</dates>
	</play>
	<play title="Beautiful - The Carole King Musical">
		<description>Beautiful is the Tony Award-winning smash-hit Broadway
			musical that tells the true story of Carole King’s journey from
			schoolgirl to superstar. It traces her relationship with her husband
			and song-writing partner Gerry Goffin, their close friendship and
			playful rivalry with fellow song-writing duo Barry Mann and Cynthia
			Weil, and her remarkable rise to stardom.

			Beautifully staged, the show
			features a uniformly excellent cast of actor /
			singers who rise to the
			challenge of executing King’s timelessly
			brilliant songs just as well
			as their Sixties forebears did. If
			you're over 45 you’ll recognise
			every single song instantly, and if
			you aren’t, get ready to enter an
			Aladdin’s cave of glittering
			musical jewels.

			It’s a particular pleasure
			to watch the songs develop from early piano or
			guitar demos to fully
			realised pop performances on stage. Beautiful
			respects the songwriting
			process and reveals it magically, in a
			moving, entertaining artist
			biography that offers real depth and
			insight into the life of one of
			modern music’s most talented and
			influential figures.
		</description>
		<dates>
			<date>2016-03-21</date>
			<date>2016-03-22</date>
		</dates>
	</play>
</tns:plays>